{
    "subject": "Michele_Lupo",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Master_Touch",
    "human_readable": "Michele Lupo directed The Master Touch.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8209543824195862,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Master Touch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7283745408058167,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Michele Lupo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6905325055122375,
            "question": "Is Michele Lupo a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6658769845962524,
            "question": "Who acted in 'The Master Touch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.596602737903595,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Michele Lupo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.539324939250946,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of a film directed by Michele Lupo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44820401072502136,
            "question": "Where was 'The Master Touch' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44798725843429565,
            "question": "When was 'The Master Touch' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3301127552986145,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Michele Lupo's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31909456849098206,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Master Touch' likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michele Lupo directed The Master Touch.",
            "html": "yago_16451_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in Michele Lupo's films?",
            "html": "yago_16451_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Master Touch' released?",
            "html": "yago_16451_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was 'The Master Touch' filmed?",
            "html": "yago_16451_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16451_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that confirms Michele Lupo directed the film \"The Master Touch\" (aka \"Un Uomo Da Rispettare\"), as evidenced by the details in multiple files."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}